export const chapter = "Chapter - 5: Different Ways of Life";
export const noOfActivities = 3;

if (localStorage.getItem("activityNumber") == 1) {
  activityData = {
    activity: "Tick the correct option:",
    questions: [
      {
        question:
          "When did the Vedic Age in the Indian subcontinent take place?",
        optionA: "1000 BC to 600 BC",
        optionB: "2000 BC to 1000 BC",
        optionC: "1500 BC to 1000 BC",
        correctAnswer: "1500 BC to 1000 BC",
      },
      {
        question:
          "What is the meaning of the word 'arya' as mentioned in the text?",
        optionA: "Common people",
        optionB: "Noble, honourable, respected",
        optionC: "Foreigners",
        correctAnswer: "Noble, honourable, respected",
      },
      {
        question:
          "Which of the Vedas is considered the oldest and is the chief source of information about the Early Vedic Age?",
        optionA: "Samaveda",
        optionB: "Yajurveda",
        optionC: "Rigveda",
        correctAnswer: "Rigveda",
      },
      {
        question:
          "How were the Vedas transmitted before they were written down?",
        optionA: "They were transmitted through letters.",
        optionB: "They were transmitted through word of mouth.",
        optionC: "They were transmitted through religious ceremonies.",
        correctAnswer: "They were transmitted through word of mouth.",
      },
      {
        question:
          "Which of the following texts is NOT mentioned as a source of information for the Later Vedic Age in the text?",
        optionA: "Brahmanas",
        optionB: "Ramayana",
        optionC: "Upanishads",
        correctAnswer: "Ramayana",
      },
      {
        question: "Where did the Vedic Age develop rapidly?",
        optionA: "South India",
        optionB: "Central India",
        optionC: "North India",
        correctAnswer: "North India",
      },
      {
        question:
          "What was the primary material used for major activities in Chalcolithic settlements?",
        optionA: "Bronze",
        optionB: "Copper",
        optionC: "Stone",
        correctAnswer: "Stone",
      },
      {
        question:
          "Which civilization discovered copper first and made the alloy of bronze by mixing zinc and copper?",
        optionA: "Chalcolithic Civilization",
        optionB: "Harappan Civilization",
        optionC: "Vedic Civilization",
        correctAnswer: "Harappan Civilization",
      },
      {
        question:
          "What is the main difference between Harappan and Chalcolithic settlements, as mentioned in the text?",
        optionA: "Chalcolithic settlements were urbanized.",
        optionB: "Harappans discovered iron first.",
        optionC: "Chalcolithic settlements were rural in nature.",
        correctAnswer: "Chalcolithic settlements were rural in nature.",
      },
      {
        question:
          "What was the primary source of information about the Chalcolithic Age in the Deccan (Central and South India)?",
        optionA: "Vedas",
        optionB: "Excavations",
        optionC: "Megalithic sites",
        correctAnswer: "Excavations",
      },
    ],
  };
}

if (localStorage.getItem("activityNumber") == 2) {
  activityData = {
    activity: "Fill in the blank with correct option:",
    questions: [
      {
        question:
          "The period known as the _______ is when books became an important source of history in the Indian subcontinent.",
        options: ["Bronze Age", "Iron Age", "Vedic Age"],
        correctAnswer: "Vedic Age",
      },
      {
        question:
          "The Aryans are said to have come to India around _______ BC, but this fact is not certain.",
        options: ["2000", "1500", "1000"],
        correctAnswer: "1500",
      },
      {
        question: "The word 'arya' means '________.'",
        options: ["common", "noble, honourable, respected", "foreign"],
        correctAnswer: "noble, honourable, respected",
      },
      {
        question:
          "The Early Vedic Age lasted from circa 1500 BC to _______ BC.",
        options: ["2000", "1000", "600"],
        correctAnswer: "1000",
      },
      {
        question:
          "The Vedas are the chief source of information about the _______.",
        options: ["Bronze Age", "Harappan Civilization", "Vedic Age"],
        correctAnswer: "Vedic Age",
      },
      {
        question:
          "The Rigveda contains 1,028 hymns in the praise of _______ and goddesses.",
        options: ["animals", "trees", "gods"],
        correctAnswer: "gods",
      },
      {
        question:
          "The chief sources of information for the Later Vedic Age include the four Vedas (Rigveda, Samaveda, Yajurveda, and Atharvaveda), as well as the Brahmanas, the Aranyakas, and the _______.",
        options: ["Upanishads", "Ramayana", "Mahabharata"],
        correctAnswer: "Upanishads",
      },
      {
        question:
          "The Chalcolithic Age in the Deccan lasted until about _______ BC.",
        options: ["4000", "2000", "1000"],
        correctAnswer: "1000",
      },
      {
        question:
          "The Chalcolithic people discovered _______ first and came to know of copper much later.",
        options: ["iron", "bronze", "gold"],
        correctAnswer: "iron",
      },
      {
        question:
          "The Harappans discovered _______ first and made the alloy of bronze by mixing zinc and copper.",
        options: ["iron", "copper", "silver"],
        correctAnswer: "copper",
      },
    ],
  };
}

if (localStorage.getItem("activityNumber") == 3) {
  activityData = {
    activity: "Write 'True' for True and 'False' for False statements:",
    questions: [
      {
        question:
          "The Arctic regions receive abundant direct sunlight throughout the year.",
        optionA: "True",
        optionB: "False",
        correctAnswer: "False",
      },
      {
        question: "Antarctica is the northern region of the Polar regions.",
        optionA: "True",
        optionB: "False",
        correctAnswer: "False",
      },
      {
        question:
          "Greenland is the largest island in the world and is part of the continent of North America.",
        optionA: "True",
        optionB: "False",
        correctAnswer: "True",
      },
      {
        question:
          "80 percent of the Greenland island is covered with grasslands.",
        optionA: "True",
        optionB: "False",
        correctAnswer: "False",
      },
      {
        question:
          "In Nuuk, the summers are cold, and the winters are warm and sunny.",
        optionA: "True",
        optionB: "False",
        correctAnswer: "False",
      },
      {
        question:
          "The Jakobshavn Glacier is one of the slowest-moving glaciers in the world.",
        optionA: "True",
        optionB: "False",
        correctAnswer: "False",
      },
      {
        question:
          "Greenland is rich in mineral resources and has fertile soil, making it suitable for agriculture.",
        optionA: "True",
        optionB: "False",
        correctAnswer: "False",
      },
      {
        question:
          "The primary occupation of the Inuit (Eskimo) people in Greenland is farming.",
        optionA: "True",
        optionB: "False",
        correctAnswer: "False",
      },
      {
        question: "The Peninsular Plateau is located in the Polar regions.",
        optionA: "True",
        optionB: "False",
        correctAnswer: "False",
      },
      {
        question:
          "The climate on the Peninsular Plateau remains moderate throughout the year, with significant differences between summer and winter temperatures.",
        optionA: "True",
        optionB: "False",
        correctAnswer: "True",
      },
    ],
  };
}

export var activityData;
